♪ I wish I knew wanted me ♪
♪ I wish I knew, I wish
I knew you wanted me ♪
♪ What you, ooh, uh, what you do ♪
♪ Made a move, coulda made a move ♪
♪ If I knew I'd be with you ♪
♪ Is it too late to pursue ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ I bite my tongue, it's a bad habit ♪
♪ Kinda mad that I didn't
take a stab at it ♪
♪ Thought you were too
good for me, my dear ♪
♪ Never gave me time of day, my dear ♪
♪ It's okay, things happen for ♪
♪ Reasons that I think are sure, yeah ♪
♪ I wish I knew, I wish
I knew you wanted me ♪
♪ I wish I knew yeah, I
wish I knew you wanted me ♪
♪ I wish I knew, I wish
I knew you wanted me ♪
♪ Say to me, please just say to me ♪
♪ If this could wind up ♪
♪ I wish you wouldn't play with me ♪
♪ I wanna know, oh no ♪
♪ Can I bite your tongue
like my bad habit ♪
♪ Would you mind if I tried
to make a pass at it ♪
♪ Were you not too good for me, my dear ♪
♪ Funny you come back to me, my dear ♪
♪ It's okay, things happen for ♪
♪ Reasons that I can't ignore, yeah ♪
♪ I wish I knew, I wish
I knew you wanted me ♪
♪ I wish I knew wish I knew ♪
♪ I wish I knew you wanted me ♪
♪ You can't surprise a Gemini ♪
♪ I'm everywhere, I'm cross-eyed, and ♪
♪ Now that you're back, I can't decide ♪
♪ If I decide if you're invited ♪
♪ You always knew the way to wow me ♪
♪ Fuck around, get tongue-tied, and ♪
♪ I turn it on, I make it rowdy ♪
♪ Then carry on, but I'm not hidin' ♪
♪ You grabbin' me hard 'cause
you know what you found ♪
♪ Is biscuits, is gravy, babe ♪
♪ You can't surprise a Gemini ♪
♪ But you know it's
biscuits, is gravy, babe ♪
♪ I knew you'd come back around ♪
♪ 'Cause you know it's
biscuits, it's gravy, babe ♪
♪ Let's fuck in the back
of the mall, lose control ♪
♪ Go stupid, go crazy, babe ♪
♪ I know I'll be in your
heart 'til the end ♪
♪ You'll miss me, don't beg me, babe ♪
(upbeat music)